United Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners of America. Local 453 (Auburn, NY) Minute Books 6280
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners of America. Local 453 (Auburn, NY) Minute Books
1888-1968
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America
UBC Local 453
6280
4 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
Minute books.
6417085
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
MValadez, January 23, 2009
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5810: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 125 (Utica, NY) Records 5810 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 125 (Utica, NY) Records on Microfilm 5819 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 1508 (Lyons, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5828: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 3211 (Herkimer, NY) Minute Books 5828 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 3211 (Herkimer, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5826: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 337 (Whitesboro, NY) Minute Books 5826 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 337 (Whitesboro, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5817 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 502 (Canandaigua, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5821 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 72 (Rochester, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5827: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Mohawk Valley District Council of Carpenters Minute Books 5827 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Mohawk Valley District Council of Carpenters Minute Books on Microfilm
Carpenters -- Labor unions -- New York -- Auburn; United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America. Local 453 (Auburn, N.Y.)
6417085
- Minute Book, 1888-1894 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Oct. 14, 1888 - April 4, 1894. First meeting, S. Galpin pres.
- Minute Book, 1894-1899 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  April 18, 1894 - June 26, 1899. Some loose papers inside cover.
- Minute Book, 1899-1901 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  July 10, 1899 - Dec. 9, 1901. Index to correspondence in back. Many loose papers inside cover.
- Minute Book, 1902-1904 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Jan. 6, 1902 - Sept. 26, 1904.
- Minute Book, 1904-1908 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Oct. 10, 1904 - Apirl 20, 1908. A few original claims for relief (doctor's notes).
- Minute Book, 1908-1912 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  May 4, 1908 - April 1, 1912. 8" x 13".
- Minute Book, 1912-1914 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  April 15, 1912 - Sept. 14, 1914. Index at end of volume.
- Minute Book, 1914-1919 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Oct. 12, 1914 - March 24, 1919.
- Minute Book, 1919-1924 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  April 7, 1919 - May 26, 1924.
- Minute Book, 1924-1928 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  June 23, 1924 - May 21, 1928. Last entry loose inside cover.
- Minute Book, 1936-1940 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  March 16, 1936 - June 17, 1940.
- Minute Book, 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  July 7, 1947 - June 17, 1949.
- Minute Book, 1949-1954 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  July 11, 1949 - Feb. 1, 1954.
- Minute Book, 1954-1959 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Feb. 15, 1954 - June 1, 1959.
- Minute Book, 1959-1964 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  June 15, 1959 - Feb. 3, 1964.
- Minute Book, 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Feb. 17, 1964 - March 4, 1968. Loose papers inside cover.
- Day Book, 1888-1890 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Nov. 15, 1888 - Dec. 17, 1890. Expenses, receipts, fund balances, member names. Very few pages.
- Day Book, 1892-1893 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  1892 (4th quarter) - April 1893. Account balances, relief expenses, membership totals, member names.
- Day Book, 1898-1900 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  April 1898 - July 1900. Same content as others.
- Day Book, 1900-1903 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  July 1900 - March 1903. Same content as others.
- Day Book, 1901-1903 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Jan. 1901 - Sept. 1903. Reports, including balance of several funds, number of members in good standing, receipts, amount of sick benefits paid. 5" x 7", red cover.
- Day Book, 1903-1905 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  March 1903 - Sept. 1905. Reports, including balance of several funds, number of members in good standing, receipts, amount of sick benefits paid.
- Day Book, 1905-1908 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Sept. 1905 - March 1908. Expenses, expenditures, including relief (with name, number of weeks, seniority number).
- Day Book, 1908-1918 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Nov. 1908 - Dec. 1918.
- Day Book, 1908-1910 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  April 1908 - Oct. 1910.
- Day Book, 1910-1912 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  Oct. 1910 - Feb. 1912. Receipts, reports, expenses.
- Day Book, 1919-1931 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  Jan. 1919 - Jan. 1931. Expenses, receipts, includes relief payments, names, and duration.
- Day Book, 1931-1943 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  March 1931 - March 1943
- Dues Payment Book, 1888-1889 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Dues Payment Book, 1890 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Dues Payment Book, 1891-1892 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Dues Payment Book, 1893-1894 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Dues Payment Book, 1895-1896 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Dues Payment Book, 1897-1898 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Dues Payment Book, 1899-1900 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Dues Payment Book, 1901-1902 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Dues Payment Book, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Dues Payment Book, 1904-1905 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Dues Payment Book, 1907-1908 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Dues Payment Book, 1908-1909 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Dues Payment Book, 1910-1911 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Dues Payment Book, 1912-1913 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Dues Payment Book, 1914-1915 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Dues Payment Book, 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Dues Payment Book, 1923-1926 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Dues Payment Book, 1930-1933 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Treasurer's Cash Book, 1896-1897 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  Jan. 1896 - Dec. 1897. Expenses, receipts, salaries, relief paid. Receipts broken up by dat only, not itemized. Small format (6" x 8"), thin.
- Treasurer's Cash Book, 1898-1899 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  Jan. 1898 - March 1899. Expenses, receipts, salaries, relief paid. Receipts broken up by dat only, not itemized. Small format (6" x 8"), thin.
- Treasurer's Cash Book, 1899-1908 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  April 1899 - Oct. 1908. Relief payments, receipts, account balances. Larger format, much thicker and more detailed.
- Immediate Relief Association, 1905-1928 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  Death benefit, contributory, paid with 24 hours of death. Two loose annual reports. Includes 1916 history of the association inside cover.
- Auburn Federation of Labor, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  Per capita taxes paid. List of member unions. Some loose papers inside volume.
- Treasurer's Cash Book, 1898-1899 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Receipts and Expenditures. January 1898-April 1899.
- Treasurer's Cash Book, 1896-1897 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Receipts and Expenditures. January 1896 - December 1897.
- Order Book, 1946-1950 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Record Book, 1908-1912 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  May 4, 1908 - April 1, 1912
- Record Book, 1899-1900 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  July 10, 1899 - June 24, 1900. Carpenters and Joiners of America. Auburn, NY.
- Journal, 1935-1952 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Different Unions.
- Record Book, 1902-1904 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Minutes. Local Union no 453 le J. of A. Auburn, NY. January 6, 1902 - 1904.
- Minute Book, 1936-1940 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America. Local Union No. 453. Auburn, NY. April 6, 1936 - June 17, 1940
- Day Book, 1900-1903 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Day Book, 1903-1905 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Day Book, 1908-1910 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  United Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners of America. Auburn, NY.
- Instructions of Financial Secretaries, 1914-1915 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Instructions to Financial Secretaries, 1904-1905 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Treasurers Leash Book, 1899-1908 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Union 453, Auburn, NY. July 1899 - October 1908
- Minutes, 1894-1899 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  April 18,1894-July 1899. Auburn, NY.
- Treasurer's Cash Book, 1904-1908 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Auburn, NY. October 10, 1904-April 6, 1908
- Minutes, 1888-1894 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America. Auburn, NY. Local Union No. 453. October 1, 1888-March 1894
- Record Book, 1914-1919 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  October 12, 1914-March 24, 1919.
- Minute Book, 1919-1924 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  April 7, 1919-May 1924.
- Minute Book, 1912-1914 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  April 15, 1912-Sept. 24, 1914 Started by Henry B. King. Auburn, NY.
- Minute Book, 1959-1964 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  June 15, 1959-February 3, 1964. United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America.
- Minute Book: Secretary Treasurer, 1954-1959 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joins of America. February 15, 1954-June 15, 1959.
- Minute Book, 1949-1954 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America. Auburn, NY. July 11, 1949-February 1954.
- Minute Book, 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America. February 17, 1964- March 4,1968.
- Minute Book, 1924-1928 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America. Auburn, NY. June 23, 1924-May 7, 1928.
- Minute Book, 1947-1949 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America. July 7, 1947-July 11, 1949
- Treasurer's Cash Book, 1919-1931 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Receipts and expenses. January 1919-January 1931
- Instructions to Financial Secretaries, 1923-1926 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  1923-1926
- Instructions to Financial Secretaries (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Instructions to Financial Secretaries (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Instructions to Financial Secretaries, 1901-1902 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  1901-1902
- Instructions to Financial Secretaries, 1899-1910 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  1899-1910
- Instructions to Financial Secretaries, 1897-1898 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  1897-1898
- Day Book, 1888-1889 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  November 1888-1889
- Day Book, 1893-1894 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  December 1893-189
- Day Book, 1898-1899 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  April 1898-1899
- Instructions to Financial Secretaries, 1888-1889 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  1888-1889
- Instructions to Financial Secretaries, 1895-1896 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  1895-1896
- Day Book, 1910-1912 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  October 1910-March 1912